Guide to the New York State College of Agriculture and Life Sciences. Office of Academic Programs records, [ca.1875]-1981.
New York State College of Agriculture and Life Sciences. Office of Academic Programs records
- Lists of Summer Session Students, 1925 (Box 23, Folder 34)
- Summer Session - General, 1918-1959 (Box 23, Folder 35)
- Summer Session - General, 1960-1970 (Box 23, Folder 36)
- Summer Session - General, 1966-1967 (Box 23, Folder 37)
- Summer Session, 1973-1976 (Box 23, Folder 38)
- Summer Session Administrative Board, 1948-1965 (Box 23, Folder 39)
- Summer Session Administrative Board, 1970-1973 (Box 23, Folder 40)
- University Faculty Committee on Student Conduct, 1945-1969 (Box 24, Folder 1)
- Discipline - General, 1923-1969 (Box 24, Folder 2)
- Delinquent Students - General, 1933-1941 (Box 24, Folder 3)
- Hotel Administration, 1931-1938 (Box 24, Folder 4)
- Conference Board of Farm Organizations, 1961-1968 (Box 24, Folder 5)
- Faculties Association, 1962-1965 (Box 24, Folder 6)
- Sigma Xi, 1961-1976 (Box 24, Folder 7)
- Phi Kappa Phi, 1962-1976 (Box 24, Folder 8)
- Cornell Credit Union, 1965-1967 (Box 24, Folder 9)
- National Science Foundation, 1958-1962 (Box 24, Folder 10)
- National Science Foundation, 1963-1973 (Box 24, Folder 11)
- Cornell Plantations, 1968-1969 (Box 24, Folder 12)
- University of the State of New York, 1969-1973 (Box 24, Folder 13)
- A Study of American Colleges of Agriculture, 1963-1964 (Box 24, Folder 14)
- Sales and Marketing Executives International, 1962-1964 (Box 24, Folder 15)
- National Secretaries Association, 1963-1969 (Box 24, Folder 16)
- Educational Testing Service, 1963-1971 (Box 24, Folder 17)
- Shell Merit Programs, 1963-1973 (Box 24, Folder 18)
- College Entrance Examination Board, 1969-1972 (Box 24, Folder 19)
- National Academy of Sciences Research Council, 1964-1967 (Box 24, Folder 20)
- Ithaca College, 1963 (Box 24, Folder 21)
- Harvard University, 1964 (Box 24, Folder 22)
- United States Office of Education, 1965-1974 (Box 24, Folder 23)
- Agency for International Development, 1967 (Box 24, Folder 24)
- Cornell University Office of Institutional Studies, 1968 (Box 24, Folder 25)
- Cornell COSEP (Committee on Special Educational Projects), 1968-1974 (Box 24, Folder 26)
- Agricultural Manpower Program, 1967-1970 (Box 24, Folder 27)
- Affirmative Action Program - College of Agriculture, 1971-1974 (Box 24, Folder 28)
- Agricultural Research - Cooperative Program, 1971-1975 (Box 24, Folder 29)
- Alumni Association - Agriculture College, 1910-1965 (Box 24, Folder 30)
- Alumni Association - Agriculture College, 1972-1974 (Box 24, Folder 31)
- Cornell Alumni Association, 1964-1970 (Box 25, Folder 1)
- Reunion - Alumni, 1969 (Box 25, Folder 2)
- Agricultural Fund, 1970-1973 (Box 25, Folder 3)
- Former Students, 1891-1923 (Box 25, Folder 4)
- Occupations of Former Students, 1923-1964 (Box 25, Folder 5)
- Graduate School - General, 1915-1968 (Box 25, Folder 6)
- Graduate School - Problems and Policies, 1965-1968 (Box 25, Folder 7)
- Graduate School - Enrollment Information, 1967-1972 (Box 25, Folder 8)
- Department of Education, 1966-1969 (Box 25, Folder 9)
- Department of Education, 1970-1976 (Box 25, Folder 10)
- Department of Education - Professor Novak, 1966-1973 (Box 25, Folder 11)
- Graduate School of Education, 1936-1976 (Box 25, Folder 12)
- Graduate School, 1971-1976 (Box 25, Folder 13)
- Graduate Faculty, 1933-1970 (Box 25, Folder 14)
- Graduate Faculty, 1972-1974 (Box 25, Folder 15)
- Ford Foundation Masters Program, 1962-1965 (Box 25, Folder 16)
- Professional Degree Program - Ormsby, 1969 (Box 25, Folder 17)
- Master's Degree Program, 1968-1970 (Box 25, Folder 18)
- Master's Degree Program Committee Minutes, 1970 (Box 25, Folder 19)
- Search Committee - Director of Libraries, 1967 (Box 25, Folder 20)
- Library - General, 1969-1976 (Box 25, Folder 21)
- University Library, 1916-1969 (Box 26, Folder 1)
- University Library, 1970-1976 (Box 26, Folder 2)
- Agricultural Association - Student Council, 1939-1975 (Box 26, Folder 3)
- Kermis Club, 1923-1964 (Box 26, Folder 4)
- Cornell Countryman, 1914 (Box 26, Folder 5)
- Cornell Countryman, 1925-1932 (Box 26, Folder 6)
- Cornell Countryman, 1933-1939 (Box 26, Folder 7)
- Cornell Countryman, 1940-1943 (Box 26, Folder 8)
- Cornell Countryman, 1914-1973 (Box 26, Folder 9)
- Student Information Service, 1973 (Box 26, Folder 10)
- Student Affairs - General, 1914-1962 (Box 26, Folder 11)
- Student Affairs - Honundekah, 1920-1968 (Box 26, Folder 12)
- Honundekah Barbecue, 1966-1976 (Box 26, Folder 13)
- Honundekah Senior Tea, 1970-1973 (Box 26, Folder 14)
- Honor Convocations, 1966-1975 (Box 26, Folder 15)
- Honor Council - General, 1926-1962 (Box 26, Folder 16)
- Honor Council - Reports, 1906-1953 (Box 26, Folder 17)
- Interfraternity Council, 1961-1964 (Box 26, Folder 18)
- 4-H Clubs, 1927-1976 (Box 26, Folder 19)
- Student Social Affairs, 1922-1946 (Box 26, Folder 20)
- Willard Straight Hall, 1921-1923 (Box 26, Folder 21)
- Frigga Fylge, 1911-1913 (Box 26, Folder 22)
- Lazy Club, 1912 (Box 26, Folder 23)
- University Freshmen Advisory System, 1916 (Box 26, Folder 24)
- Agricultural College Fraternities, 1954 (Box 26, Folder 25)
- Alpha Zeta, 1962-1976 (Box 26, Folder 26)
- Alpha Gamma Rho, 1921-1969 (Box 26, Folder 27)
- Gamma Sigma Delta, 1961-1965 (Box 26, Folder 28)
- Delta Tau Alpha, 1962 (Box 26, Folder 29)
- Scarab, 1934 (Box 26, Folder 30)
- Agricultural College Student Council, 1968-1971 (Box 26, Folder 31)
- Student Candidates for Faculty Committees, 1972-1973 (Box 26, Folder 32)
- Student-Faculty Administration Luncheons, 1960-1965 (Box 26, Folder 33)
- National Block and Bridle Round-Up Club (Box 26, Folder 34)
- Student Government, 1963-1965 (Box 26, Folder 35)
- Student Health Services, 1966-1970 (Box 26, Folder 36)
- Cornell Association of Teachers of Agriculture (Box 26, Folder 37)
- Pre-Medical Student, 1970-1975 (Box 27, Folder 1)
- Agricultural Associations - General, 1962 (Box 27, Folder 2)
- Association of Land Grant Colleges, 1943-1959 (Box 27, Folder 3)
- Association of Land Grant Colleges, 1960-1973 (Box 27, Folder 4)
- American Association of University Professors, 1968-1971 (Box 27, Folder 5)
- RICOP (Resident Instruction Committee on Organization and Policy), 1956-1963 (Box 27, Folder 6)
- RICOP, 1964-1966 (Box 27, Folder 7)
- Northeast Region - Deans and Directors of Resident Instruction, 1955-1962 (Box 27, Folder 8)
- Northeast Region - Deans and Directors of Resident Instruction, 1962-1965 (Box 27, Folder 9)
- Association of State Universities and Land-Grant Colleges - Resident Instruction, 1960-1962 (Box 27, Folder 10)
- Association of State Universities and Land-Grant Colleges - Resident Instruction, 1963-1967 (Box 27, Folder 11)
- National Institute of Health, 1963 (Box 27, Folder 12)
- Grange, 1960-1976 (Box 27, Folder 13)
- G.L.F., 1920-1964 (Box 27, Folder 14)
- International Institute of Agriculture, 1956 (Box 27, Folder 15)
- Agricultural Experimenters League of New York, 1907 (Box 27, Folder 16)
- Agricultural Businessmen's Council, 1960-1970 (Box 27, Folder 17)
- Food and Agriculture Organization of the United Nations, 1960-1964 (Box 27, Folder 18)
- Wine Producers - General, 1961-1962 (Box 27, Folder 19)
- New York State Agricultural Society, 1962-1976 (Box 27, Folder 20)
- Council on Rural Education, 1962 (Box 27, Folder 21)
- New York State Flower Growers, 1962 (Box 27, Folder 22)
- New York State Council of Farmer Cooperatives, 1962 (Box 27, Folder 23)
- Association of Teachers of New York, 1960-1976 (Box 27, Folder 24)
- United States Department of Agriculture, 1969-1973 (Box 27, Folder 25)
- School of Education Council, 1963-1964 (Box 27, Folder 26)
- Future Farmers of America, 1976 (Box 27, Folder 27)
- National Association of Colleges and Teachers of Agriculture, 1965-1972 (Box 27, Folder 28)
- Agricultural and Technical Institutes, 1922-1964 (Box 27, Folder 29)
- Agricultural and Technical Institutes, 1968-1976 (Box 27, Folder 30)
- Department of Health, Education and Welfare, 1970 (Box 27, Folder 31)
- Commission on Education and Natural Resources, 1970 (Box 27, Folder 32)
- National Farm School and Junior College, 1946-1967 (Box 28, Folder 1)
- Institute of Food Science and Marketing, 1967-1977 (Box 28, Folder 2)
- Cooperative Extension Service, 1919-1975 (Box 28, Folder 3)
- Cooperative Extension Service, 1923-1973 (Box 28, Folder 4)
- County Agents, 1964-1971 (Box 28, Folder 5)
- Junior Field Days, 1927 (Box 28, Folder 6)
- Correspondence Courses, 1905-1967 (Box 28, Folder 7)
- Radio Station, 1930-1974 (Box 28, Folder 8)
- Agriculture Experiment Station, 1923-1972 (Box 28, Folder 9)
- Purnell Act, 1925 (Box 28, Folder 10)
- Grants for Research, 1921-1973 (Box 28, Folder 11)
- College of Agriculture in Relation to War, 1918 (Box 28, Folder 12)
- Lists of Students in War Service, 1917 (Box 28, Folder 13)
- Lists of Faculty Members in War Service, 1917 (Box 28, Folder 14)
- Forms Used for Certification, 1918 (Box 28, Folder 15)
- Draft Classification, 1918-1969 (Box 28, Folder 16)
- Record of War Work in Emergency Courses, 1917 (Box 28, Folder 17)
- Students Army Training Corps, 1918 (Box 28, Folder 18)
- Staff in War Service, 1942 (Box 28, Folder 19)
- College Memorabilia, 1900-1954 (Box 28, Folder 20)
- Charles Palm Dinner, 1972 (Box 28, Folder 21)
- Annual Report College of Agriculture, 1935-1936 (Box 28, Folder 22)
- Annual Report College of Agriculture, 1937-1939 (Box 28, Folder 23)
- Annual Report College of Agriculture, 1940-1941 (Box 28, Folder 24)
- Annual Report College of Agriculture, 1941-1942 (Box 28, Folder 25)
- Annual Report College of Agriculture, 1942-1943 (Box 28, Folder 26)
- Annual Report College of Agriculture, 1943-1944 (Box 28, Folder 27)
- Annual Report College of Agriculture, 1944-1945 (Box 28, Folder 28)
- Annual Report College of Agriculture, 1945-1946 (Box 28, Folder 29)
- Annual Report College of Agriculture, 1946-1947 (Box 28, Folder 30)
- Annual Report College of Agriculture, 1947-1948 (Box 28, Folder 31)
- Annual Report College of Agriculture, 1948-1949 (Box 28, Folder 32)
- Annual Report College of Agriculture, 1949-1950 (Box 28, Folder 33)
- Annual Report College of Agriculture, 1950-1951 (Box 28, Folder 34)
- Annual Report College of Agriculture, 1951-1952 (Box 28, Folder 35)
- Annual Report College of Agriculture, 1952-1954 (Box 28, Folder 36)
- Annual Report College of Agriculture, 1954-1955 (Box 29, Folder 1)
- Annual Report College of Agriculture, 1955-1957 (Box 29, Folder 2)
- Annual Report College of Agriculture, 1957-1958 (Box 29, Folder 3)
- Annual Report College of Agriculture, 1958-1959 (Box 29, Folder 4)
- Annual Report College of Agriculture, 1959-1961 (Box 29, Folder 5)
- Annual Report College of Agriculture, 1961-1962 (Box 29, Folder 6)
- Annual Report College of Agriculture, 1962-1964 (Box 29, Folder 7)
- Annual Report College of Agriculture, 1964-1966 (Box 29, Folder 8)
- Annual Report College of Agriculture, 1966-1968 (Box 29, Folder 9)
- Annual Report College of Agriculture, 1968-1969 (Box 29, Folder 10)
- College of Agriculture Reports, 1924-1926 (Box 29, Folder 11)
- College of Agriculture Reports, 1928-1934 (Box 29, Folder 12)
- College of Agriculture Reports, 1937 (Box 29, Folder 13)
- College of Agriculture Reports, 1938 (Box 29, Folder 14)
- McDonald Farm Advisory Committee, 1961-1963 (Box 29, Folder 15)
- Committee to Improve Service to Teachers, 1955-1957 (Box 29, Folder 16)
- Committee to Study Objectives and Policies Agriculture Program, 1962-1964 (Box 29, Folder 17)
- Cornell University Alumni Committee on Secondary Schools, 1958-1965 (Box 29, Folder 18)
- Intersession Committee, 1967-1968 (Box 29, Folder 19)
- Agribusiness Symposium - Purdue University, 1962 (Box 29, Folder 20)
- Oral History Advisory Committee, 1963-1971 (Box 29, Folder 21)
- National Short Course Committee, 1963 (Box 29, Folder 22)
- Committee on Alumni-Faculty, 1963-1964 (Box 29, Folder 23)
- RICOP, 1963-1965 (Box 29, Folder 24)
- RICOP, 1965-1967 (Box 29, Folder 25)
- College of Agriculture Program Review, 1963 (Box 29, Folder 26)
- Orientation and Advising Committee, 1964-1970 (Box 29, Folder 27)
- Honors Program and Independent Study Committee, 1967-1970 (Box 29, Folder 28)
- President's Committee on Biological Sciences, 1964 (Box 29, Folder 29)
- Committee on the Future of the College of Agriculture, 1964-1967 (Box 29, Folder 30)
- Committee on Systematic Collections, 1964 (Box 29, Folder 31)
- Faculty Committee on Undergraduate Scholarships, 1959-1961 (Box 29, Folder 32)
- University Faculty Committee on Long Range Planning, 1959 (Box 29, Folder 33)
- ESCOP (Experiment Station Committee on Organization and Policy), 1965 (Box 29, Folder 34)
- Committee on Undergraduate Programs Abroad, 1965 (Box 29, Folder 35)
- Undergraduate Programs Abroad, 1961-1967 (Box 29, Folder 36)
- Grading System Committee, 1965-1970 (Box 29, Folder 37)
- Educational Environment, 1965 (Box 29, Folder 38)
- Entrance Standards Committee, 1965 (Box 29, Folder 39)
- Dropout Problem Committee, 1965 (Box 29, Folder 40)
- Intercollege Transfers, 1964 (Box 29, Folder 41)
- Articulation of Undergraduate Studies with Programs of Secondary Schools, 1964 (Box 29, Folder 42)
- Committee on Quality of Undergraduate Instruction, 1965-1968 (Box 29, Folder 43)
- Committee on Educational Programs - Goals of the College, 1959 (Box 29, Folder 44)
- Committee on Physics, 1959-1961 (Box 29, Folder 45)
- University Faculty on Registration and Schedules, 1961-1968 (Box 29, Folder 46)
- President's Committee to Study the State College of Agriculture, 1965 (Box 29, Folder 47)
- Pimentel Committee, 1967 (Box 29, Folder 48)
- American Meat Institute Fall Conference, 1968 (Box 30, Folder 1)
- Data Gathered for Reply to Miscellaneous Inquiries, 1926-1976 (Box 30, Folder 2)
- Corson Questionnaire - Planning Projections, 1964 (Box 30, Folder 3)
- New York State Land Use Committee, 1940 (Box 30, Folder 4)
- New York State Agricultural Resources Commission, 1969-1972 (Box 30, Folder 5)
- War, 1942-1950 (Box 30, Folder 6)
- Post-War Planning (World War II), 1943-1944 (Box 30, Folder 7)
- Staff and Facilities Used for Army and Navy Programs, 1943-1945 (Box 30, Folder 8)
- Farm and Home Week, 1952-1969 (Box 30, Folder 9)
- Agricultural Leaders' Forum, 1971-1973 (Box 30, Folder 10)
- Conservation Leaders' Forum, 1970-1973 (Box 30, Folder 11)
- Natural Resource Organizations, 1972 (Box 30, Folder 12)
- International Agricultural Development, 1962-1963 (Box 30, Folder 13)
- International Agricultural Development, 1963-1964 (Box 30, Folder 14)
- International Agricultural Development, 1964-1965 (Box 30, Folder 15)
- International Agricultural Development, 1965-1970 (Box 30, Folder 16)
- Countries - Liberia (Box 30, Folder 17)
- Countries - Philippines, 1955-1965 (Box 30, Folder 18)
- International Agricultural Advisory Committee, 1969-1972 (Box 30, Folder 19)
- International Agricultural Advisory Committee, 1972-1974 (Box 30, Folder 20)
- Council on International Education Exchange, 1969-1970 (Box 30, Folder 21)
- Veterinary College, 1962-1973 (Box 30, Folder 22)
- Farm Youth Program, 1961 (Box 30, Folder 23)
- Radioisotopes, 1961-1962 (Box 31, Folder 1)
- High School Natural Science Program, 1959-1969 (Box 31, Folder 2)
- Agricultural Science Youth Program, 1960-1969 (Box 31, Folder 3)
- Programmed Learning, 1962 (Box 31, Folder 4)
- Special Studies: Chemistry, 1960-1962 (Box 31, Folder 5)
- Honors Program, 1960-1972 (Box 31, Folder 6)
- Honors Program, 1972-1974 (Box 31, Folder 7)
- Honors Program, 1974-1976 (Box 31, Folder 8)
- College Open House, 1959-1975 (Box 31, Folder 9)
- Land-Grant Centennial Convocation, 1962 (Box 31, Folder 10)
- Peace Corps Program, 1961-1967 (Box 31, Folder 11)
- Peace Corps Program, 1969-1970 (Box 31, Folder 12)
- Peace Corps Program, 1970-1976 (Box 31, Folder 13)
- First Year Students Dropped, 1961-1962 (Box 31, Folder 14)
- Applications from High School National Science Program Students, 1962 (Box 31, Folder 15)
- High School Social Science Program, 1962-1965 (Box 31, Folder 16)
- Orientation of Foreign Graduate Students in Agriculture, 1958-1961 (Box 31, Folder 17)
- Orientation of Foreign Graduate Students in Agriculture, 1961-1976 (Box 31, Folder 18)
- A Study of Enrollment In the College of Agriculture, 1961-1962 (Box 31, Folder 19)
- International Voluntary Services, 1962-1972 (Box 31, Folder 20)
- College of Agriculture Departmental Enrollment, 1957-1965 (Box 31, Folder 21)
- Undergraduate Housing, 1962 (Box 31, Folder 22)
- Grade Distribution, 1961-1963 (Box 31, Folder 23)
- Students in 2-Year Agriculture Program, 1959-1960 (Box 31, Folder 24)
- Profile of Graduates of College of Agriculture, 1962 (Box 31, Folder 25)
- Advisers of Graduates, 1962 (Box 31, Folder 26)
- Student Attrition in College of Agriculture, 1962 (Box 31, Folder 27)
- College of Agriculture Faculty, 1963 (Box 31, Folder 28)
- Financial Aid Awarded to Undergraduate Students, 1961-1963 (Box 31, Folder 29)
- Other Courses Taken by Agriculture Students, 1962 (Box 31, Folder 30)
- Students with SAT Scores Below 400, 1963 (Box 31, Folder 31)
- High School Guidance Counselors' Program, 1967-1971 (Box 31, Folder 32)
- Adjusted High School Average, 1963 (Box 32, Folder 1)
- Farm Experience of Entering Students, 1915-1969 (Box 32, Folder 2)
- Statistics on the Ithaca Faculty - College of Agriculture, 1964 (Box 32, Folder 3)
- Need for Agricultural Historian, 1964 (Box 32, Folder 4)
- Scandinavian Seminar, 1964-1969 (Box 32, Folder 5)
- Cornell Latin America Year, 1964-1965 (Box 32, Folder 6)
- Source of Degrees of Faculty Members, 1965 (Box 32, Folder 7)
- Petitions to Lower Number of Required Electives, 1965 (Box 32, Folder 8)
- National Colonial Farm, 1967 (Box 32, Folder 9)
- Social Sciences at Cornell, 1967 (Box 32, Folder 10)
- Selective Service Outlines, 1968-1971 (Box 32, Folder 11)
- Selective Service, 1966-1972 (Box 32, Folder 12)
- Department Heads, 1960-1965 (Box 32, Folder 13)
- Cornell University Water Resources Center, 1958-1966 (Box 32, Folder 14)
- Center for International Studies, 1966-1970 (Box 32, Folder 15)
- Center for International Studies, 1971-1977 (Box 32, Folder 16)
- Life Sciences Center, 1962-1963 (Box 32, Folder 17)
- Reading-Study Center, 1963 (Box 32, Folder 18)
- Computer Services, 1969 (Box 32, Folder 19)
- Computer Services, 1970 (Box 32, Folder 20)
- Computer Services, 1971-1974 (Box 32, Folder 21)
- Computer Activities Group, 1962-1972 (Box 32, Folder 22)
- Instructional Computer Requests, 1971-1972 (Box 32, Folder 23)
- Open Access Computing, 1973-1975 (Box 32, Folder 24)
- Center for Improvement of Undergraduate Education, 1972-1974 (Box 32, Folder 25)
- Cornell Research Foundation, 1969 (Box 32, Folder 26)
- Cornell Aeronautical Laboratory, 1967-1968 (Box 32, Folder 27)
- Student Lists, 1960-1965 (Box 32, Folder 28)
- Bakia Club, 1963-1967 (Box 32, Folder 29)
- Cornell Research Park, 1968 (Box 33, Folder 1)
- Fire Drill Committee, 1967-1971 (Box 33, Folder 2)
- Cornell Association of Agriculture Teachers, 1968-1971 (Box 33, Folder 3)
- Labor Relations Act, 1969-1972 (Box 33, Folder 4)
- Cornell United Fund, 1968-1970 (Box 33, Folder 5)
- Faculty Advisory System Committee, 1950-1951 (Box 33, Folder 6)
- Report for the Middle States Association of Colleges, 1957 (Box 33, Folder 7)
- Report for the Middle States Association of Colleges, 1957 (Box 33, Folder 8)
- Middle States Association Part B Questionnaire, 1956 (Box 33, Folder 9)
- Distribution by Counties of Students Entering the College of Agriculture, 1945-1956 (Box 33, Folder 10)
- Students Interested in Teaching Vocational Agriculture, 1948 (Box 33, Folder 11)
- Record of Students Accepted from Private Preparatory Schools, 1949-1955 (Box 33, Folder 12)
- Study of Freshman Entering the College of Agriculture, 1942-1953 (Box 33, Folder 13)
- Various Factors to Success in the College of Agriculture, 1938-1940 (Box 33, Folder 14)
- Relation of Various Factors to Grades in College of Agriculture, 1946-1955 (Box 33, Folder 15)
- Study of Occupations of Former Students, 1941 (Box 33, Folder 16)
- Training High School Teachers of Vocational Agriculture, 1954 (Box 33, Folder 17)
- Tuition Letters, 1952 (Box 33, Folder 18)
- Reports to the Senate, 1954 (Box 33, Folder 19)
- Replies from Advisers, 1955 (Box 33, Folder 20)
- Comparison of Former Students, 1925 (Box 33, Folder 21)
- Class of 1912 Reunion, 1936 (Box 33, Folder 22)
- Comparison of Deceased Graduates and Non-Graduates (Box 33, Folder 23)
- Gibson - Study of Former Students, 1880-1920 (Box 33, Folder 24)
- Relation of Farm Experience to Scholarship and Mentat Test Scores, 1920-1926 (Box 33, Folder 25)
- Letters Concerning the Alumni Directory, 1924 (Box 33, Folder 26)
- Occupations of Agricultural Students - Miscellaneous (Box 33, Folder 27)
- Comparison of Students in College of Agriculture, 1914-1924 (Box 33, Folder 28)
- Graduates Specializing in Forestry, Botany,Landscape Architecture (Box 33, Folder 29)
- Value of Farm Experience for Graduates in Agricultural Business, 1910-1923 (Box 33, Folder 30)
- Report on Supervised Reading Group, 1937 (Box 33, Folder 31)
- Papers Read at Land Grant College Association Meeting, 1928 (Box 33, Folder 32)
- Committee on Aims and Purposes of the College, 1923 (Box 33, Folder 33)
- Resident Instruction - Problems, 1937-1942 (Box 33, Folder 34)
- Interviews with Dairy Concerns, 1930 (Box 33, Folder 35)
- Eaton's Study - Teaching in the College of Agriculture, 1923 (Box 33, Folder 36)
- Enrollment in Land Grant Colleges, 1926-1937 (Box 33, Folder 37)
- Interest Analysis, 1930 (Box 33, Folder 38)
- Marketing Fruits and Vegetables, 1930 (Box 33, Folder 39)
- Students of Bacteriology - Hours of Instruction, 1937 (Box 33, Folder 40)
- Study of 1929 Orientation Class, 1933 (Box 33, Folder 41)
- Study of Two Year Course Work, 1937 (Box 34, Folder 1)
- Grades of Two-Year Students, 1933 (Box 34, Folder 2)
- First Term Record of Men Admitted, 1934 (Box 34, Folder 3)
- Occupational Choices, 1929 (Box 34, Folder 4)
- Vocational Purposes of Students, 1933 (Box 34, Folder 5)
- Historical Interest, 1910-1955 (Box 34, Folder 6)
- Bailey Questionnaire to Foreign Students, 1905 (Box 34, Folder 7)
- Evaluation - University of Maryland, 1953-1955 (Box 34, Folder 8)
- Teaching Grant Proposals, 1965-1966 (Box 34, Folder 9)
- Counseling and Guidance Training, 1963-1964 (Box 34, Folder 10)
- NSF (National Science Foundation) Program for Elementary School Grades, 1962 (Box 34, Folder 11)
- NSF Undergraduate Research Participation, 1958-1967 (Box 34, Folder 12)
- Summer Institute for Secondary School Teachers, 1963-1965 (Box 34, Folder 13)
- NSF Undergraduate Instructional Scientific Equipment Program, 1961-1964 (Box 34, Folder 14)
- National Center for Advanced Study in Agricultural Education, 1961-1962 (Box 34, Folder 15)
- NSF Grants, 1962-1965 (Box 34, Folder 16)
- NSF Grants, 1962-1965 (Box 34, Folder 17)
- NSF Grants, 1962-1965 (Box 34, Folder 18)
- NSF Grants, 1962-1965 (Box 34, Folder 19)
- NSF Grants, 1962-1965 (Box 34, Folder 20)
- Teacher Education and Certification, 1960 (Box 34, Folder 21)
- Traffic, 1960 (Box 34, Folder 22)
- Report on Student Housing, 1950 (Box 34, Folder 23)
- State Schools of Agriculture, 1936 (Box 34, Folder 24)
- Minutes of Publications Committee, 1940-1945 (Box 34, Folder 25)
- Minutes of Publications Committee, 1946-1960 (Box 34, Folder 26)
- Minutes of Publications Committee, 1958-1965 (Box 34, Folder 27)
- Budget Reports for College of Agriculture, 1929-1940 (Box 35, Folder 1)
- Budget for Agricultural Experiment Station - Geneava, NY, 1939-1943 (Box 35, Folder 2)
- Report of Committees Presented to the College Conference, 1919 (Box 35, Folder 3)
- Survey of Resident Teaching and Administration, 1928 (Box 35, Folder 4)
- Survey of the Extension Services, 1928 (Box 35, Folder 5)